Guide to the Jeremy Ayers Papers MSS.610
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Visual Arts, 1923-2017; 1990-2016; 9.35 Linear Feet in 13 legal boxes, 1 flat box, 4 oversized flat boxes, 4 flat file folders, 1 cassette box, and a card box; 106.626 Gigabytes in 12,276 digital files
  - Subseries I.D: Artwork, 1980-2017; 1980-2000; 3.30 Linear Feet in 3 manuscript boxes, 1 flat box, 2 oversized flat boxes, and a flat file folder
    - Photographs of Jeremy Ayers' Artwork, undated, 2007, 2014-2017
      - Printed Photographs, undated (Box 10, Folder 2-3)
      - Digital Photographs, 2007, 2014-2017; FA_MSS_610_ER_60
    - R.E.M. "Pageantry" Tour Program (Artwork by Jeremy Ayers), circa 1980 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Sketchbook, undated (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Slides of Jeremy Ayers' Artwork, 1986, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Transparencies of Jeremy Ayers' Artwork, undated (Box 10, Folder 5, Box 32, Folder 1)
- Series II: Writings, 1974-2017; 1989-1995; 9.8 Linear Feet in 18 manuscript boxes and 3 oversized flat boxes; 0.7 Gigabytes in 169 digital files
  Series II contains Jeremy Ayers' original writings and include screenplays like The Gravedigger's Story (circa 1990), Lonestar Moon (1995-1997), and Passengers (1996-1998); manuscript drafts including The Lost Forest (undated); short stories such as The Bindle Sticks (2013) and Rudolph, or the Revelations of a famous Reindeer (2015); and loose notes and notebooks with written prose and song lyrics. This series also contains Ayers' journals, dated from 1974 through 2014, which document his daily life, his thoughts, and sometimes include creative pieces. Digital copies of Ayers' writings, notes, outlines, and drafts are also included in this series.
  Materials have been arranged in alphabetical order. Untitled journals have been further arranged into chronological order.
  - Article by Jeremy Ayers from the Athens Observer, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Give Back My Beast, 2014; FA_MSS_610_ER_61
  - Benny & Charlie, 2017; FA_MSS_610_ER_62
  - The Bindle Stick, 2013; FA_MSS_610_ER_68
  - Canray Poole Play, 2010, 2015-2016; FA_MSS_610_ER_66
  - The Gravedigger's Story, circa 1990 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Handwritten Notes -- Occupy Wall Street, circa 2011 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Handwritten Notes and Prose, undated (Box 10, Folder 7-9, Box 11, Folder 1-3, Box 32, Folder 4, Box 34, Folder 10, Box 35, Folder 12-13, Box 37)
  - Journals, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 4, Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Journals, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Journals, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Journals, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 1-2)
  - Journals, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 3-5)
  - Journals, 1990-1992 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Journals, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Journals, 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Journals, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Journals, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Journals, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Journals, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 5-6)
  - Journals, 2014 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Journals, undated (Box 14, Folder 1-5, Box 15, Box 16, Folder 1-6, Box 17, Box 18, Folder 1-3)
  - Journals -- Ace, undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Journals -- Address Books, undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Journals -- Breathing Time, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Journals -- Calliope, undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Journals -- Distillery, undated (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Journals -- Film Festival Addresses, undated (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Journals -- Fool Tophat Bottle Books, undated (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Journals -- Gardening, undated, circa 1989 (Box 19, Folder 5-7)
  - Journals -- Infinitely, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Journals -- Jody's Hang Book, undated (Box 19, Folder 2-3)
  - Journals -- Lewis Merriweather, undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Journals -- Lonestar Moon: The Guidance Club, undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Journals -- Reading Notes, undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Journals -- Reading Notes and Travel, undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Journals -- Song Lyrics, undated (Box 20, Folder 8, Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Journals -- Song Lyrics -- "Cut to the Chase", 1995 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Journals -- The Story of the Horse and the Woman, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Journals -- Yoga, undated (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - The Kite, 2017; FA_MSS_610_ER_70
  - Lone Star Moon, 1995-1997, 2008, 2017
    - Printed Materials, 1995-1997 (Box 22, Folder 1-6, Box 23, Folder 1-2)
    - Digital Materials, 2008, 2017; FA_MSS_610_ER_63
  - The Lost Forest, undated, 2008-2009, 2013-2017
    - Printed Materials, undated (Box 23, Folder 3-5, Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Digital Materials, 2008-2009, 2013-2017; FA_MSS_610_ER_64
  - Of Philpot's Raggart, undated (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Old Story, undated (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Passengers, 1996-1998, 2006, 2017
    - Printed Materials, 1996-1998 (Box 24, Folder 1-6, Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Digital Materials, 2006, 2017; FA_MSS_610_ER_65
  - Research Materials with Handwritten Notes, undated (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Rudolph, or Revelations of a famous Reindeer, 2015; FA_MSS_610_ER_67
  - The Sleeper, 2006, 2010-2017; FA_MSS_610_ER_71
  - Song Lyrics, undated, 2010
    - Printed Materials, undated (Box 31, Folder 6-7)
    - Digital Materials, 2010; FA_MSS_610_ER_69
  - There's No Halloween in Paris, undated (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Untitled Works, circa 1998, 2009-2016
    - Printed Materials, circa 1998 (Box 25, Folder 2-4)
    - Digital Materials, 2009-2016; FA_MSS_610_ER_72
  - Will You Go Out With Me?, undated (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Series III: Personal Materials, 1919-2018; 1980-2017; 5.08 Linear Feet in 7 manuscript boxes, 1 flat box, 3 oversized flat boxes, and a LP box; 11.04 Gigabytes in 6,837 digital files
  Series III focuses on Jeremy Ayers as an individual and contains items relating to his personal life. Materials include Ayers' vintage photograph, postcard, and stamp collections; Ayers' collection of art by other artists; ephemera from the Occupy Wall Street movement such as a cardboard Fox News microphone used by protestors and posters; Ayers' passports, yoga certificates, and astrological reports; short biographies used in exhibitions and publications; personal correspondence between Ayers and friends; the written works of friends and family members; photographs of Ayers' family and childhood; digital photographs of the interior of his home and his personal belongings; and electronic back-ups of Ayers' Facebook profile and email inbox. Materials in this series are in paper and digital formats.
  Materials in this series are arranged in alphabetical order by personal names, general topic, and publication titles. For publications with listed authors, these materials have been arranged alphabetically by the author's name, followed by the publication titles.
  - Andy Warhol's Factory and Sylvia Thinn (News clippings), circa 1970s (Box 26, Folder 1, Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Art Book Collection, 2017; FA_MSS_610_ER_73
  - Artwork Collected by Jeremy Ayers, undated, 2016
    - Paper Materials, undated (Box 33, Folder 9-10, Box 34, Folder 7-12, Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Digital Materials, 2016; FA_MSS_610_ER_74
  - Ayers, Jeremy -- Astrology Chart, undated (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Ayers, Jeremy -- Biography, undated (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Ayers, Jeremy -- Certificates, 2008 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Ayers, Jeremy -- Facebook Backups, 2013-2017; FA_MSS_610_ER_78
  - Ayers, Jeremy -- Home, Garden, and Personal Items, 2012-2017; FA_MSS_610_ER_80
  - Ayers, Jeremy -- Passports, 1982-2008 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Ayers, Robert H. -- "Memoirs of a Southern Liberal", undated (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Beach Lady Memorial, undated; FA_MSS_610_ER_1
  - Business Cards Collected by Jeremy Ayers, undated (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Contract -- B-52s, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Contract -- R.E.M., 1985 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence -- Emails to Jeremy Ayers, 1999-2001, 2018
    - Printed Materials, 1999-2001 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Digital Materials, 2018; FA_MSS_610_ER_77
  - Correspondence -- Envelopes Only, 1989-1998, 2011 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence -- From Jeremy Ayers, undated (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence -- To Jeremy Ayers, 1977-2011, 2017
    - Printed Materials, 1977-2011 (Box 26, Folder 9-12, Box 27, Folder 1-5, Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Digital Materials, 2017; FA_MSS_610_ER_75
  - Email Addresses, 2006-2007; FA_MSS_610_ER_76
  - Engagement Announcement for Jeremy Ayers' Parents (Press Clipping), 1941 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Exhibition Announcements (Jeremy Ayers and Others), undated, 1980, 2010-2014 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Exhibition Press and Promotional Materials (about Jeremy Ayers), 2002 (Box 28, Folder 1, Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Family Photographs and Negatives, 1919-2017
    - Printed Materials, 1919-1987 (Box 28, Folder 2-7)
    - Digital Materials, 2007, 2013, 2016-2017; FA_MSS_610_ER_79
  - The Finster Family Show Poster, undated (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Fischerspooner -- Egos Photography Book, 2015 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Flurry, Alan -- "Flip", undated (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Free Fall, 2011-2012 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - "Homenaje a Mama" Vinyl Record, 1976 (Box Shared Fales 104, Folder 4)
  - Howard Finster's Vision of 1982 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Journal of Cosmic Wizardry, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Münch, Christopher -- "Sunday's Carnations", 1988 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Newman, Bruce -- "Body Pressure", 1974 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Notes Found in Books, undated (Box 29, Folder 9-10)
  - Occupy Wall Street -- Flyer, circa 2011 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Occupy Wall Street -- Fox News Microphone Prop, circa 2011 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Occupy Wall Street -- "People Over Profit" Bracelet, circa 2011 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Occupy Wall Street -- Posters, circa 2011 (Box 34, Folder 16, Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Personal and Research Statements, 2016; FA_MSS_610_ER_81
  - Photographs by S.L. Phipps, 2010-2013 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Photograph Album, undated (Box 30, Folder 2-3)
  - Sling Shot International Music Festival (Athens, Georgia), 2014; FA_MSS_610_ER_82
  - Spanish Arts and Culture Festival, 2010 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Stamp Collection, 1962, circa 1980-2000 (Box 30, Folder 4-5)
  - Thornsberry, Vernon J. -- The Angry Man, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Vintage Photograph Collection, undated (Box 30, Folder 7-8)
  - Vintage Postcard Collection, undated (Box 30, Folder 9, Box 31, Folder 1-4)
  - Writings by Daniel Nelson, 2008-2009; FA_MSS_610_ER_83